five years ago this Alex G that you know
of today what's the largest profit you
made in a single day of trading
$121,000 in one single day didn't exist
he was a young 18-year-old kid that was
immature unsuccessful and extremely lost
and 5 years later all of this changed
completely and this is due to the fact
that he took action on doing the duties
to become successful he decided to stop
being a child and messing around on and
wasting time and take responsibility on
what had to be done to be successful
from that day forward and be successful
for the rest of his life and although it
wasn't easy trust me it is definitely
worth it and all of this started when I
decided to take responsibilities for my
life and that was to make important
decisions decisions like to plan my life
my every single step of my day my
calendar Everything plan every single
thing that I had to do and this year I
have already planned my whole entire
year from start to finish and in this
video I'm going to officially commit
myself and share with you guys what I
have planned for this year and I came up
with these goals at a private retreat
that I had at the beginning of the year
to really come down to the core things
that would help myself and everybody
around me now before I tell you my goals
the only reason why I'm putting it out
here on YouTube and documenting it is
because every single time I want to
achieve something I document it and then
when you fast forward 2 3 years later
you can see the result cuz I'm
manifesting it every single day for
example you can take this video right
here of me looking at a McLaren where
I'm saying that I'm going to achieve it
2 years from that day fast forward 2
years about my first McLaren 720 and
examples like these I have hundreds of
them and right before I get started with
the goals in this video I don't want you
to think that I'm just here flexing on
you or just making this video about me
I'm just showing to you guys how a
23-year-old that 5 years ago was that
Dunkin Donuts can make big plans and
Achieve them I'm doing this to inspire
you guys so you guys have ambition so
you guys can set goals for yourselves
and you can achieve them within the year
so I'm doing this to show you guys what
I'm planning and how I'm going to
achieve it and what I'm going to do to
do it so you can set goals for yourself
and you can do the same so now that you
understand that whatever I put my mind
to I will achieve it this is my first
goal and my first goal is as crazy as
this might sound is I will be buying a
jet before 2024 ends now I know that
might sound crazy that a 23-year-old
that was 5 years ago working at Dunkin
Donuts is going to own a jet and the
answer is yes and the reason why I'm
taking action on this is because in 2023
I took over 60 to 70 flights all around
the world and I realized that I hate
airports I simply hate waiting in line I
hate having to deal with other people in
the airport and you waste so much time
waiting for the plane to come Miss
flight or not yeah not dealing with any
of that stuff anymore time is an asset
and I'm going to use that to my
advantage with my own private plane can
just call up the pilot pull up fly
Whenever However I want so you might be
wondering how I'm going to achieve
buying a Jet and I'm going to actually
explain that to you later in the video
it's going to be part of my fifth goal
so make sure you watch the video to the
end so you understand how I'm going to
be able to afford a jet as a 23y old but
my main goal with buying this jet is
simply saving time and not actually ual
you know 2 hours or 3 hours on a flight
it's more of like mental space not
having to deal with the airport not
having to deal with the delayed flight
not having to deal with possible
interactions in the airport you know
everybody that's flying everybody's
stressed everybody's in a rush you know
it's just not a good environment so it's
just to save that head space of having
to deal with all of that so I can simply
always be in Focus mode I don't ever
have to get out of that mode moving on
to my next goal which is going to sound
even crazier is my extreme bucket list
so now what does this mean so if you
guys don't know I love adrenaline I
think life is meant to go have fun not
to just be home and watching Netflix and
bbard all the time like if you're
successful the point is you have free T
to go have fun go do fun not just
simply be home doing nothing so my
second goal is achieve everything in my
extreme bucket list which is going to
consist of four things so the first goal
in the extreme bucket list is going to
be for me to compete in a real rally
race so if you guys don't know I a
semi-pro professional Drifter I love
racing I love cars I love all of that
stuff and as a kid I've always seen
these guys racing through the woods and
just drifting and I just think it's
awesome because they're getting these
street cars but they're making them
allterrain so one of my goals this year
is to compete in a real rally race where
I'm so serious about it that I even
bought a canm you know a semi rally car
for me to practice in so I can train and
be prepared for when I go race later
this year and and I think it's going to
be around October or November race
that's going to happen in Europe the
second goal within my extreme bucket
list is going to be doing a backflip off
of a wake boarding boat so I've actually
never wakeboarded in my life I have
never even done any sports inside the
water and I've always wanted to do a
backflip but I feel like a backflip is
pretty basic so why not do it off of a
wakeboarding boat and you know probably
you know just something crazy so I
bought a boat and I've already been
practicing how to wakeboard and it's
harder than you might think so I've been
getting the practice of it and uh I'm
going to be working towards that all
summer so I'm able to successfully land
and do a back flip while I'm
wakeboarding and I know this second one
might seem like a weird or random one
but who do you know that can do a back
flip off of a wakeboarding boat probably
nobody so I want to be that guy my third
goal within my extreme bucket list is
going to be to race in the it's kind of
even crazy for me to say it's for me to
race in the mountain of hell so it's a
competitive race that is done on
bicycles that is started at the top of a
mountain somewhere in Denver or
somewhere in Aspen Colorado where you
race from a top of a Snowy Mountain you
race down it where you then go through a
Terrain of woods and then you race
through the city of wherever the race is
going to be held so this is a Health
Challenge that I'm going to set for
myself because you need to be an extreme
shape in order to be able to pretty much
race down a mountain that you're up
20,000 25,000 ft on top of a mountain
and then most importantly then be able
to go back up it through the terrain
it's an extreme adrenaline rush and it's
done only one time a year so I'm going
to be training all year for me to be
able to successfully to not only compete
in it but potentially land in a higher
ranking of it and then last but not
least my fourth goal of my extreme
bucket list is going to be jumping off
of a plane so skydiving and then maybe
solo skydiving I am extremely scared of
heights and I am a believer that you
have to face your fears in order for you
to to realize that it's not that bad and
you know you're bigger than what you're
scared of and I'm something that I'm
going to be mentally preparing myself
this year and I will be giving it a shot
because I just believe you have to face
your fears and I have never ever in my
life thought I'd ever be able to do it
but I will be doing that this year so
I'm setting all of these challenges as
one of my goals in my extreme blocket
list because I really do believe that if
you are successful you are to experience
everything out there you are to do
anything and everything that is possible
we're not getting any younger and our
time is limited so just make sure you
live life to the fullest and I'm going
to make sure I do that this year and I
do plan to achieve it because the year
has just started and I already bought
pretty much the race car and I already
bought the boat so now I have to do is
buy the bike and then just you know get
some balls when I'm ready to jump out
the plane so I'm working very hard to
achieve all these goals so moving on
from our extreme bucket list is my third
goal which is actually something that I
have already kind of been doing but I'm
going to take extremely serious this
year and that is going to be be set and
forget philanthropy so I'm going to be
starting a my philanthropy where I'll be
giving back to schools where I'll be
helping kids in need their kids in
cancer my family and friends that I have
in Cuba probably you know help them give
school supplies to some kids out there
that literally have nothing help some
kids in Africa help some cancer kids
that are as well here in the United
States my goal is to just help those
people that are truly in need and they
don't have access to anything they're
not able to get access to resources so
they can better the situation so that's
where I'm going to be taking set and
forget philanthropy where it's going to
be bettering the situation because I
have the possibility to do it and I have
been giving back since the beginning of
my first success that I have had with
trading and I almost think that it's
fair because trading is you know
obviously very easy work once you learn
the skill set and if I have the
possibility to give back those in need I
think it's only fair if I'm able to give
back and also one of the main reasons on
why I'm pursuing this is because I
remember one time that I was at a red
light here in Miami and and there was a
lady selling oranges or I think it was
some type of fruit and I asked her how
much was it for her whole entire set of
fruits and I think she asked like $50 I
give her $1,000 there at the red light
and this lady has completely bald and
tears she said that I had cleared her
debth for the whole entire last 6 months
she has had a credit card depth of $700
and that that was stressing her out she
didn't know how she was going to pay it
and it was only getting bigger because
the interest was obviously eating her up
and when she ex like I literally felt
her expression she told me to get out
the car and give her a hug and ever
since I felt that from that day that
something so small to me was so big to
that person I figured that it's only
fair if I continue to chase this feeling
and change somebody's life and better
the situation so now going into to our
fourth goal we all know I am a Trader
and I've been trading now for five six
years and the fourth goal is trading
related and this is to bust any myth out
there that you can't take trading not
only big but you can take it to the next
level where you are extremely successful
as a retail Trader or as a Trader from
your home office just a regular person
just trading at home giving it 100%
every single day with a profitable
strategy and that's why my fourth goal
is to make $10 million this year from my
personal account using my set and forget
strategy and the reason why I have the
10 million doll Mark as the goal is
because that's pretty much the next
thing kind of after a million obviously
the millions have been made I've been
very close to almost the 8 figure Mark
but not quite there alone from my
trading so this year is to make 10
million solely and simply from my
trading and I don't plan to just achieve
this on my own by myself you know in my
office I plan to show you guys this
whole entire Journey for the past four
to 3 years every single trade that I
have taken has been publicated on
telegram YouTube Instagram and Discord
every every single trade that I have
taken and this year not only am I going
to turn it up a notch but I'm going to
show you guys how I'm going to make this
$10 million right in front of you guys
with every single trade that it take
everything is going to be documented so
you guys can see the journey and what it
took to make that Amun amount of money
oh and you think I forgot about the
first goal yeah my goal is that halfway
through the year I should be halfway
through this goal where it's $5 million
so I will get about 60 to 75% of that
and we throw it straight into a jet so
that's how I'm going to be affording the
jet this year in 2024 so I will be
killing two birds with one stone or two
goals with one trading goal so we're
going to see how that goes and last but
not least which is my fifth goal which
is by far my most important and most
challenging goal that I will be taking
on this year is with you guys my set and
forget community and my students and
that is going to be for my set and
forget students to make the same amount
or even more than I do this year but the
goal is for the set and forget community
to make over $10 million this year and I
want you guys to understand the degree
of the difficulty that it takes for that
to happen for me to make $10 million
this year in trading it's not difficult
because I am responsible for that it's
just one person and I know what it takes
and I've been doing this for 6 years and
I've already made multiple seven figures
from Trading so I just replicate it and
I know the system that works and I'm
100% dedicated to the craft but now
managing thousands of students every
single day in my chat takes extreme
organization takes extreme dedication
and it takes extreme consistency and
respect towards the set and foret
strategy not only is it the most
challenging and difficult goal out of
this whole entire big five but it is
also the most fulfilling one knowing
that a strategy that I simply created in
the closet of my parents house 5 to four
years ago trying to figure out what
trading was to now where Traders all
around the world will be part of
something bigger than I am
that to me is extremely powerful and the
reason why I'm doing this is because I
remember when I got started trading
there wasn't a big Community out there
there wasn't proof that trading was real
there wasn't a strategy that worked
nonetheless a community or a mentor that
cared about every single person that was
out there so once s and forget grew to
what it is today which is the number one
trading community in the industry like
well this comes with great
responsibility and I can't just take it
for granted or simply not treat it with
respect that's why I'm going to make it
my goal to make this bigger than I am
and the way how I plan to do this is not
only am I going to continue to do the
weekly calls with my students I'm going
to add a Rewards program inside of my
Discord I'm going to add multiple
educational videos and I'm also going to
add a day trading section inside of
Swing training lab so you can take my
strategy use it for swing trading and
you can also use it for day trading in
addition to that we're going to also
have weekly Q&A calls and we're going to
also have students that are going to
host calls in there themselves so my
most profitable students they're going
to be given a role inside the chat where
then they can also Mentor people at a
more detailed Point aside from what I'm
already going to be doing with you guys
on a weekly basis in order for this goal
to be achieved I'm literally going to
fire everything everything that I have
all of my ammunition everything that I
use even my psychology my mindset
everything is going to be put on the
table to be able to achieve this goal
because it is one of the most difficult
one and if that isn't enough we're going
to host two annual in-person masterminds
for only and exclusively for set and
forget students this way so we can also
see each other in person and get to know
the other people that are being part of
something bigger than dumb it's just
something that is going to be like
nothing I ever seen before and that is
because I'm going to be opening my swing
trading Lab podcast where I'm going to
be doing an interview with every single
Trader that makes money within the set
forget community and we're going to have
a board where we're going to obviously
track the profits of every single Trader
with payout proof with withdraws crypto
addresses bank statements everything so
everything has a foolproof system I'm
going to do an interview with every
single person that gets a payout cuz
then that goes towards the bigger goal
of $10 million this year so you guys can
learn from these students and how they
got set in for GU strategy and how they
implemented it into their lives whether
they had a full-time job whether they
were working online whether they had no
idea what trading was or whether they
simply added it to their day-to-day life
and they use trading as a side income so
everything is going to be documented not
only within the chat but there's going
to be a separate YouTube channel where
we are going to show the interviews and
the successful and profitable traders
that are parts of the $10 million goal
so as you guys can see there's a lot
that's going to be happening this year
and I want this to be motivational to
you guys inspirational if I am able to
make it get out of Dunkin Donuts not
only become a successful Trader but now
have such big goals with such planning
and not only make it about me it's about
everybody around me use this as a form
of motivation for you to do this as well
so I'm extremely excited for you guys to
be part of this process and you guys see
what is going to happen this year so if
you want to become a set and forget
Trader if you're probably wondering what
is set and forget and how make students
make anywhere from ,000 to $1,500 a week
as a beginner set and forget Trader
click the link in the description below
there's a video for there that explains
for you exactly what it consists of how
Traders are making anywhere from $1,000
to $1,500 a week as a beginner Trader in
the first 3 months using the set and
forget strategy watch the video let me
know what you guys think it is exactly
the key Foundation of what set and
forget means so appreciate you guys
watching the video all the way to the
end let's let 2024 begin